Eleanor Dickinson collection
American Folklife Center, Library of Congress
- Series II: Sound recordings
  - AFC 1970/001: SR003, September 1, 1978, 1 sound cassette; 60 min.
    Hymn singing, Sevier County Old Harp Singers, Wears Valley, Tennessee. Probably the same church and singers in tapes SR001-SR004. The tape is broken. Accrual part 13: "Old Harp Singing." No original ID number.
  - AFC 1970/001: SR004, September 1, 1978, 1 sound cassette
    Sevier County Old Harp Singers, Wears Valley, Tennessee. The tape was broken, but repaired by an LC engineer to make a digital transfer. Accrual part 13: "Old Harp Singing." No original ID number.
  - AFC 1970/001: SR005, August 31, 1981, 1 sound cassette; 45 min.
    Radio; religious programs. Performers on the radio, in Tennessee and Virginia. Revival preaching, country-style hymn singing. The reference copy is on side A of a 90-minute tape. Accrual part 13: "2 Misc. Tapes, Revivals." Original ID CA-81-J.
  - AFC 1970/001: SR006, August 15, 1981
    The original tape is missing from the tape shell (possibly CA-81-G, recorded August 15, 1981, "Nashville to Kentucky" -- a radio program recorded by Dickinson). For more information see Accrual part 13: "2 Misc. Tapes, Revivals."
  - AFC 1970/001: SR007, September 5, 1981, 1 sound cassette; 90 min.
    Interview (with Dewey Chafin?) on revivals, evening service, snake hunt. Dickinson and Church of The Lord Jesus interviewees, Jolo, West Virginia. Side A: interview. Side B: definition of revival vs. evangelism. The remainder of the original recording is blank. Accrual part 13: "Serpent Handling Churches." Original ID CA-81-K-1.
  - AFC 1970/001: SR008, September 5, 1981, 1 sound cassette; 90 min.
    Homecoming, cane-brake rattlers, Georgia diamondbacks "singing." Musicians, preacher, singer, interviewer: "rural poor," in one of the serpent-handling churches, Jolo, West Virginia. Side A: amplified percussive music, sermon, and discussion on handling snakes. Side B: outdoors discussion (unintelligible), music, discussion of rattlesnakes. Accrual part 13: "Serpent handling churches." Original ID CA-82-K-2.
  - AFC 1970/001: SR009, September 5, 1981, 1 sound cassette; 90 min.
    Interviews after Homecoming, evening service. Eleanor Dickinson, men (one may be Dewey Chafin), serpent-handling church, Jolo, West Virginia. Side A: music, interview about God and the devil, being saved, serpent-handling, plans for serpent hunt. Side B: discussion with two men about snakes, the faith to handle them, nine gifts and five signs, healing; evening service, percussive music. Only 1/4 of side taped. Accrual part 13: "Serpent handling churches." Original ID CA-81-K-3.
  - AFC 1970/001: SR010, September 6-7, 1981, 1 sound cassette; 90 min.
    Continuation of evening service: holiness singing, prayers, testimony, revival preacher, congregation, Church of the Lord Jesus, Jolo, West Virginia. Side A: preaching, music (followed by a blank gap in the tape), music, testimonies of healing; Side B: testimonies, music, conversations on porch, discussion of snake habits, church characteristics. Accrual part 13: "Serpent handling churches." Original ID CA-81-L-1.
  - AFC 1970/001: SR011, September 7, 1981, 1 sound cassette; 45 min.
    Discussion of medical symptoms of snake bites. Dewey and Claire Chafin, Jolo, West Virginia. Reference tape all on side A. Legal issues and snakes in church (followed by a long blank gap), discussion of dead snakes, various symptoms from different types of snake bites. Accrual part 13: "Serpent handling churches." Original ID CA-81-L-2.
  - AFC 1970/001: SR012, September 7, 1981, 1 sound cassette; 90 min.
    Discussion: location of serpent-handling churches, serpents rattling, family discussions, packing up rattlesnakes in boxes after church, getting snake from taxidermist. Dewey Chafin and others, Jolo, West Virginia. "Serpent handling churches." Accrual part 13. Original ID CA-81-M-1.
  - AFC 1970/001: SR013, August 2, 1981 or September 7, 1981, 1 sound cassette; 45 min.
    Finster; Dewey Chafin, Jolo, West Virginia. "Serpent handling churches." Accrual part 13. Original ID CA-81-M-2.
  - AFC 1970/001: SR014, September 7, 1981, 1 sound cassette; 45 min.
    Eleanor Dickinson interviewing Dewey Chafin. Dewey Chafin, Jolo, West Virginia. "Serpent handling churches." Accrual part 13. Original ID CA-81-M-3.
  - AFC 1970/001: SR015, September 8, 1981, 1 sound cassette; 90 min.
    Jolo, West Virginia. The recording has a squeaky background sound, from the original recording. Accrual part 13: "Serpent handling churches." Original ID CA-81-N.
  - AFC 1970/001: SR016, September 9, 1981, 1 sound cassette; 90 min.
    Prayer meeting. Rev. Bob Elkins, Church of the Lord Jesus, Jolo, West Virginia. "Serpent handling churches." Accrual part 13. Original ID CA-81-O.
  - AFC 1970/001: SR017, August 15, 1981 or September 9, 1981, 1 sound cassette
    The audio concordance gives September 9, 1981, as recording date. Accrual part 13. Original ID CA-81-P.
  - AFC 1970/001: SR018, July 4, 1980, 1 sound cassette; 90 min.
    Douglas Jeffords, Mount Le Conte, Tennessee. Accrual part 9. Original ID CA-81-I-1
  - AFC 1970/001: SR019, August 8, 1980, 1 sound cassette; 60 min.
    Uncle Lem Owenby, J.T. Higdon, Eleanor Dickinson, Elkmont, Tennessee. Accrual part 9. Original ID CA-80-N-1
  - AFC 1970/001: SR020, October 1, 1981, 1 sound cassette
    WSIX Radio Interview (Tennessee State Museum meeting). James Meldriari. Accrual part 9. Original ID CA-81-B-1
  - AFC 1970/001: SR021, March 31, 1981, 1 sound cassette; 90 min.
    Tennessee State Museum meeting. Accrual part 9. Original ID CA-81-B2
  - AFC 1970/001: SR022, October 21, 1981, 1 sound cassette; 90 min.
    Tennessee State Museum Southeast Museum Conference. Accrual part 9. Original ID CA-81-Q-1
  - AFC 1970/001: SR023, October 24, 1981, 1 sound cassette; 90 min.
    Tennessee State Museum. Gatlinburg, Tennessee. Accrual part 9. Original ID CA-81-S
  - AFC 1970/001: SR024, August 23, 1982, 1 sound cassette; 60 min.
    Rev. Howard Finster, Middlesboro, Kentucky. Accrual part 9. Original IDs A-82-and A-1
  - AFC 1970/001: SR025, August 23, 1982, 1 sound cassette; 90 min.
    Rev. Howard Finster and Brother H.H. Mayes, Middlesboro, Kentucky. Accrual part 9. Original IDs A-82-and A-2
  - AFC 1970/001: SR026, August 23, 1982, 1 sound cassette; 90 min.
    Rev. Howard Finster and Brother H.H. Mayes, Middlesboro, Kentucky. Accrual part 9. Original IDs A-82-and A-3
  - AFC 1970/001: SR027, August 24, 1982, 1 sound cassette; 90 min.
    Beverly Finster, Rev. Howard Finster, Eleanor Dickinson, in the car. Accrual part 9. Original ID A-82-B-1
  - AFC 1970/001: SR028, August 24, 1982, 1 sound cassette; 90 min.
    Brother H.H. Mayes and Rev. Howard Finster. Accrual part 9. Original ID A-82-B-2
  - AFC 1970/001: SR029, August 24, 1982, 1 sound cassette
    Also may be Brother H.H. Mayes and Rev. Howard Finster. See Accrual part 9 for details. Possibly original ID A-82-B-2; paired with SR030.
  - AFC 1970/001: SR030, undated, 1 sound cassette; 90 min.
    Pete Seeger concert. Accrual part 9. Original ID A-82-C-1.
  - AFC 1970/001: SR031, undated, 1 sound cassette; 90 min.
    Singing songs. Doug Jeffords, Bob Smith, Eleanor Dickinson, Elkmont, Tennessee. Accrual part 9. Original ID A-82-C-2.
  - AFC 1970/001: SR032, April 3, 1983, 1 sound cassette; 90 min.
    Easter Sunday. Rev. Hester, New Light Missionary Baptist Church. Accrual part 9. No original ID number.
  - AFC 1970/001: SR033, August 11, 1983, 1 sound cassette; 90 min.
    Interview with Uncle Lem Owenby, J.T. Higdon, Eleanor Dickinson, Elkmont, Tennessee. Accrual part 9. No original ID number.
  - AFC 1970/001: SR034, August 11, 1983 or August 14, 1983, 1 sound cassette; 90 min.
    Evelyn Gilder Creekmore; Brother H.H. and Sister Lillie Mayes, Elkmont, Tennessee. Accrual part 9. No original ID number.
  - AFC 1970/001: SR035, August 14, 1983, 1 sound cassette; 90 min.
    Brother H.H. and Sister Lillie Mayes, Middlesboro, Tennessee. Accrual part 9. No original ID number.
  - AFC 1970/001: SR036, August 3, 1983, 1 sound cassette; 90 min.
    Christian Rollin Emmit, Savannah, Georgia. Accrual part 9. No original ID number.
  - AFC 1970/001: SR037, August 3, 1983, 1 sound cassette; 90 min.
  - AFC 1970/001: SR038, July 29, 1983, 1 sound cassette; 90 min.
    Uncle Lem Owenby and niece Midge Higdon, Elkmont, Tennessee. Accrual part 9. No original ID number.
  - AFC 1970/001: SR039, July 29, 1983, 1 sound cassette; 90 min.
    Uncle Lem Owenby. Only one side recorded. Accrual part 9. No original ID number.
  - AFC 1970/001: SR040, July 27, 1983, 1 sound cassette; 90 min.
    Douglas Heinsohn, Elkmont, Tennessee. Accrual part 9. No original ID number.
  - AFC 1970/001: SR041, July 28, 1983, 1 sound cassette; 90 min.
    Jean Schilling and Lee Schilling, Cosby, Tennessee. Accrual part 9. No original ID number.
  - AFC 1970/001: SR042, July 7, 1983, 1 sound cassette; 90 min.
    Rev. Roger Powell, Church of God of the Mount Assembly, Lake City, Tennessee. Accrual part 9. Original IDs A-84 and ID A-1.
  - AFC 1970/001: SR043, July 7-9, 1984, 1 sound cassette; 90 min.
    Rev. Roger Powell, Church of God of the Mount Assembly, Lake City, Tennessee. Accrual part 9. Original ID A-84-B-1.
  - AFC 1970/001: SR044, July 10, 1984, 1 sound cassette; 90 min.
    Rev. Howard Finster, Georgia. Accrual part 9. Original ID A-84-C-1.
  - AFC 1970/001: SR045, July 8-9, 1984, July 11, 1984, 1 sound cassette; 90 min.
    Revival. Rev. Roger Powell; Rev. Howard Finster, Lake City, Tennessee; Summerville, Georgia. Accrual part 9. Original ID A-84-D-1.
  - AFC 1970/001: SR046, July 12, 1984, 1 sound cassette; 90 min.
    Rev. Howard Finster; Garrett. Accrual part 9. Original ID A-84-E-1.
  - AFC 1970/001: SR047, July 12, 1984, 1 sound cassette; 90 min.
    Rev. Howard Finster. Accrual part 9. Original ID A-84-E-2.
  - AFC 1970/001: SR048, July 14, 1984, 1 sound cassette; 90 min.
    Carlton Garrett. Accrual part 9. Original ID A-84-F-1.
  - AFC 1970/001: SR049, July 20, 1984, 1 sound cassette; 90 min.
    Bluegrass. Rusty Grass Band, on the front porch, in Cosby, Tennessee. Accrual part 9. Original ID A-84-G-1.
  - AFC 1970/001: SR050, July 20, 1984, 1 sound cassette; 90 min.
    Bluegrass. Rusty Grass Band, on the front porch, in Cosby, Tennessee. Accrual part 9. Original ID A-84-G-2.
  - AFC 1970/001: SR051, July 22, 1984, 1 sound cassette; 90 min.
    Rev. Roger Powell, Lake City, Tennessee. Accrual part 9. Original ID A-84-H-1.
  - AFC 1970/001: SR052, July 22-23, 1984, 1 sound cassette; 90 min.
    Footwashing and Lord's Supper. Rev. Roger Powell, Lake City, Tennessee. Accrual part 9. Original ID A-84-H-2.
  - AFC 1970/001: SR053, July 22-23, 1984, 1 sound cassette; 90 min.
    Interviews. Rev. Roger Powell; Brother H.H. and Sister Mayes, Lake City, Tennessee; Middlesboro, Kentucky. Accrual part 9. Original ID A-84-H-3.
  - AFC 1970/001: SR054, July 23, 1984, 1 sound cassette; 90 min.
    Brother H.H. and Sister Mayes, Middlesboro, Kentucky. Accrual part 9. Original ID A-84-I-1.
  - AFC 1970/001: SR055, July 22-23, 1984, 1 sound cassette; 90 min.
    Brother H.H. and Sister Mayes, Middlesboro, Kentucky. Accrual part 9. Original ID A-84-I-2.
  - AFC 1970/001: SR056, July 23, 1984, 1 sound cassette; 90 min.
    Interviews; religious radio. Brother H.H. Mayes, Middlesboro, Kentucky; Kentucky and West Virginia. Accrual part 9. Original ID A-84-1-3.
  - AFC 1970/001: SR057, July 25, 1984, 1 sound cassette; 90 min.
    Music; Testimonials. Rev. Ray Stuart, Church of Jesus, Besoco, WV. Accrual part 9. Original ID A-84-J-1.
  - AFC 1970/001: SR058, July 25-26, 1984, 1 sound cassette; 90 min.
    Service; interviews. Bill Spencer; Rev. Ray Stuart; Roy Garrettson; Donald Spencer, Church of Jesus, Besoco, West Virginia. Accrual part 9. Original ID A-84-K-1.
  - AFC 1970/001: SR059, July 26, 1984, 1 sound cassette; 90 min.
    Interviews. Bill Spencer; Rev. Ray Stuart; Roy Garrettson; Donald Spencer, Church of Jesus, Besoco, West Virginia. Accrual part 9. Original ID A-84-K-2.
  - AFC 1970/001: SR060, July 26, 1984, 1 sound cassette; 90 min.
    Interviews. Church of Jesus, Besoco, West Virginia. Accrual part 9. Original ID A-84-K-3.
  - AFC 1970/001: SR061, August 1, 1981, 1 sound cassette; 90 min.
    Beth Coffelt, interviewer. Rev. Howard Finster, Summerville, Georgia. Accrual part 13: "Howard Finster Tapes." Original ID CA-81-E-1.
  - AFC 1970/001: SR062, August 1, 1981, 1 sound cassette; 90 min.
    Rev. Howard Finster, Summerville, Georgia. The recording quality was affected by weak batteries, resulting in a slow tape. Accrual part 13: "Howard Finster Tapes." Original ID CA-81-E-2.
  - AFC 1970/001: SR063, August 1, 1981, 1 sound cassette; 45 min.
    Rev. Howard Finster, Summerville, Georgia. Accrual part 13: "Howard Finster Tapes." Original ID CA-81-E-3.
  - AFC 1970/001: SR064, August 1, 1981, 1 sound cassette; 45 min.
    Rev. Howard Finster, Summerville, Georgia. Accrual part 13: "Howard Finster Tapes." Original ID CA-81-E-4.
  - AFC 1970/001: SR065, August 2, 1981, 1 sound cassette; 45 min.
    Talks with local people--opinions of Rev. Howard Finster; Eleanor Dickinson and Beth Coffelt. Rev. Howard Finster, Summerville, Georgia. Accrual part 13: "Howard Finster Tapes." Original ID CA-81-F-1.
  - AFC 1970/001: SR066, August 2, 1981, 1 sound cassette; 45 min.
    Rev. Howard Finster, Georgia. The battery ran down, so the recording is garbled and fast. Accrual part 13: "Howard Finster Tapes." Original ID CA-81-F2.
  - AFC 1970/001: SR067, August 2, 1981, 1 sound cassette; 45 min.
    Rev. Howard Finster, Georgia. The initial part of the recording is affected by a bad battery. Accrual part 13: "Howard Finster Tapes." Original ID CA-81-F3.
  - AFC 1970/001: SR068, November 15, 1981, 1 sound cassette; 90 min.
    Tennessee State Museum opening of "Revival." Rev. Howard Finster; Jean Schilling and Lee Schilling; Fiddlin' Arthur Smith, Nashville, Tennessee. Accrual part 13: "Howard Finster Tapes." Original ID CA-81-P-1.
  - AFC 1970/001: SR069, November 15, 1981, 1 sound cassette; 90 min.
    Tennessee State Museum opening of "Revival." Nashville, Tennessee. Accrual part 13: "Howard Finster Tapes." No original ID number.
  - AFC 1970/001: SR070, 1981, 1 sound cassette; 90 min.
    Tennessee State Museum. Ed and Phil, Nashville, Tennessee. Dickinson marking on original indicate that recording is side 3 and 4 in a series of audio recordings. Accrual part 13: "Howard Finster Tapes." No original ID number.
  - AFC 1970/001: SR071, August 25, 1982, 1 sound cassette; 90 min.
    "Paradise Garden." Rev. Howard Finster, Summerville, Georgia. Accrual part 13: "Howard Finster Tapes."Original ID A-82-C-3.
  - AFC 1970/001: SR072, July 18, 1985, 1 sound cassette; 90 min.
    Interview, Rev. Howard Finster, Summerville, Georgia (Pennville). Accrual part 13: "Howard Finster Tapes." No original ID number.
  - AFC 1970/001: SR073, July 18, 1985, 1 sound cassette; 90 min.
    Interview, Rev. Howard Finster, Summerville, Georgia. 3 and 4, continued. Accrual part 13: "Howard Finster Tapes." Original ID A-85.
  - AFC 1970/001: SR074, July 18, 1985, 1 sound cassette; 90 min.
    Interview, Rev. Howard Finster, Summerville, Georgia. 5 and 6, continued. Accrual part 13: "Howard Finster Tapes." Possibly original ID A-85, continued.
  - AFC 1970/001: SR075, July 19, 1985, 1 sound cassette; 90 min.
    Interview, Rev. Howard Finster, Summerville, Georgia. 1 and 2. Accrual part 13: "Howard Finster Tapes." Possibly original ID A-85, continued.
  - AFC 1970/001: SR076, July 19, 1985, 1 sound cassette; 90 min.
    Homer Rathbon singing. Interview; country music, the front porch. Rev. Howard Finster, Summerville, Georgia; Cosby, Tennessee. Accrual part 13: "Howard Finster Tapes." Possibly original ID A-85, continued.
  - AFC 1970/001: SR077, 1987, 1 sound cassette
    Blank tape (as noted by an LC audio engineer). Two Dickinson numbers are written on the tape--A-87-C-1 and A-87-B-4; listed as a recording of Rev. Howard Finster. Accrual part 13: "Howard Finster Tapes."
  - AFC 1970/001: SR078, July 10, 1990, 1 sound cassette
    Rev. Howard Finster. Accrual part 13: "Howard Finster Tapes." Original ID A-90.
  - AFC 1970/001: SR079, July 10, 1990, July 16, 1990, 1 sound cassette; 90 min.
    Creekmore interview; religious radio; Rev. Howard Finster. Evelyn Creekmore; Rev. Howard Finster, Elkmont, Tennessee. Due to a bad battery the tape slowed down and the recording was affected. Accrual part 13: "Howard Finster Tapes." Original ID A-90.
  - AFC 1970/001: SR080, July 16, 1990, 1 sound cassette; 90 min.
    Rev. Howard Finster, Summerville, GA. 2 and 3; 3 garbled first 1/4 (low batteries so the recording was slow); erratic--sometimes OK. Accrual part 13: "Howard Finster Tapes." Original ID A-90.
  - AFC 1970/001: SR081, July 16-17, 1990, 1 sound cassette; 90 min.
    Rev. Howard Finster. 4: 7-16-90; 1: 7-17-90. Accrual part 13: "Howard Finster Tapes." Original ID A-90.
  - AFC 1970/001: SR082, July 17, 1990, 1 sound cassette; 90 min.
    Rev. Howard Finster. 2 and 3. Accrual part 13: "Howard Finster Tapes." Original ID A-90.
  - AFC 1970/001: SR083, July 25, 1991, 1 sound cassette; 90 min.
    Rev. Howard Finster; Eleanor Dickinson; Steven Wicks, Summerville, GA. 1; Steve Wicks, curator of Knoxville Museum of Art. Accrual part 13: "Howard Finster Tapes." Original ID A-91.
  - AFC 1970/001: SR084, July 25, 1991, 1 sound cassette; 90 min.
    Rev. Howard Finster. 2. Accrual part 13: "Howard Finster Tapes." Original ID A-91.
  - AFC 1970/001: SR085, July 25, 1991, 1 sound cassette; 90 min.
    Rev. Howard Finster. 3. Accrual part 13: "Howard Finster Tapes." Original ID A-91.
  - AFC 1970/001: SR086, 1 sound cassette
    The tape's content is not relevant to the collector's activities.
- Series III: Graphic materials
  - AFC 1970/001: PH01-18, 3 in. x 5 in. photographic prints; black and white (File 5/1)
    Images of serpent-handling, probably in Jolo, West Virginia.
  - AFC 1970/001: PH19-35, 35mm positive transparencies; color (File 5/2)
    Images from the Tennessee State Museum exhibition, "Revival!" See folder 2/4 for information about the exhibition.
- Series IV: Moving image items
  - AFC 1970/001: MV001, 1 videoreel (32 min., 57 sec.): 5 in. (diameter), 1⁄2 in. (width)
    Roadside signs, Brother Powell, Lake City, Tennessee. Original ID # V-76-A-1.
  - AFC 1970/001: MV002, 1 videoreel (32 min., 10 sec.): 5 in. (diameter), 1⁄2 in. (width)
    Pappy Beaver's Revival #1. Original ID # V-76-B-1.
  - AFC 1970/001: MV003, 1 videoreel (33 min., 52 sec.): 5 in. (diameter), 1⁄2 in. (width)
    Pappy Beaver's Revival #2. Original ID # V-76-B-2.
  - AFC 1970/001: MV004, 1 videoreel (0 min.): 5 in. (diameter), 1⁄2 in. (width)
    Pappy Beaver's Revival #3. Original ID # V-76-B-3.
  - AFC 1970/001: MV005, 1 videoreel (32 min., 15 sec.): 5 in. (diameter), 1 in. (width)
    Sevierville Church of God; House of Prayer for All People. Original ID # V-76-C-1.
  - AFC 1970/001: MV006, 1 videoreel (31 min., 15 sec.): 5 in. (diameter), 1 in. (width)
    Newport Tent Revival #1. Original ID # V-76-D-1.
  - AFC 1970/001: MV007, 1 videoreel (31 min., 55 sec.): 5 in. (diameter), 1 in. (width)
    Newport Tent Revival #2. Original ID # V-76-D-2.
  - AFC 1970/001: MV008, 1 videoreel (32 min., 7 sec.): 5 in. (diameter), 1⁄2 in. (width)
    Newport Tent Revival #3. Original ID # V-76-D-3.
  - AFC 1970/001: MV009, 1 videoreel (31 min., 15 sec.): 5 in. (diameter), 1⁄2 in. (width)
    Newport Tent Revival #4. Original ID # V-76-D-4.
  - AFC 1970/001: MV010, 1 videoreel (31 min., 8 sec.): 5 in. (diameter), 1⁄2 in. (width)
    Newport Tent Revival #5. Original ID # V-76-D-5.
  - AFC 1970/001: MV011, 1 videoreel (32 min.): 5 in. (diameter), 1⁄2 in. (width)
    Camp Creek #1. Original ID # V-76-E-1.
  - AFC 1970/001: MV012, 1 videoreel (31 min., 11 sec.): 5 in. (diameter), 1⁄2 in. (width)
    Camp Creek #2. Original ID # V-76-E-2.
  - AFC 1970/001: MV013, 1 videoreel (31 min., 43 sec.): 5 in. (diameter), 1⁄2 in. (width)
    Camp Creek #3. Original ID # V-76-E-3.
  - AFC 1970/001: MV014, 1 videoreel (30 min., 19 sec.): 5 in. (diameter), 1⁄2 in. (width)
    Camp Creek #4. Original ID # V-76-E-4.
  - AFC 1970/001: MV015, 1 videoreel (ca. 32 min.): 5 in. (diameter), 1⁄2 in. (width)
    Camp Creek #5 and travel. Original ID # V-76-E-5.
  - AFC 1970/001: MV016, 1 videoreel (32 min., 40 sec.): 5 in. (diameter), 1⁄2 in. (width)
    Brother H.H. Mayes #1. Original ID # V-76-F-1.
  - AFC 1970/001: MV017, 1 videoreel (32 min., 41 sec.): 5 in. (diameter), 1⁄2 in. (width)
    Brother H.H. Mayes #2. Original ID # V-76-F-2.
  - AFC 1970/001: MV018, 1 videoreel (32 min., 39 sec.): 5 in. (diameter), 1⁄2 in. (width)
    Brother H.H. Mayes #3. Original ID # V-76-F-3.
  - AFC 1970/001: MV019, 1 videoreel (32 min., 54 sec.): 5 in. (diameter), 1⁄2 in. (width)
    Brother H.H. Mayes #4. Original ID # V-76-F-4.
  - AFC 1970/001: MV020, 1 videoreel (32 min., 55 sec.): 5 in. (diameter), 1⁄2 in. (width)
    Brother H.H. Mayes #5. Original ID # V-76-F-5.
  - AFC 1970/001: MV021, 1 videoreel (29 min., 30 sec.): 5 in. (diameter), 1⁄2 in. (width)
    Brother H.H. Mayes #6. Original ID # V-76-F-6.
  - AFC 1970/001: MV022, 1 videoreel (30 min.): 5 in. (diameter), 1⁄2 in. (width)
    Brother H.H. Mayes #7. Original ID # V-76-F-7.
  - AFC 1970/001: MV023, 1 videoreel (32 min.): 5 in. (diameter), 1⁄2 in. (width)
    Brother H.H. Mayes #8. Original ID # V-76-F-8.
  - AFC 1970/001: MV024, 1 videoreel (32 min., 6 sec.): 5 in. (diameter), 1⁄2 in. (width)
    Jean Schilling and Lee Schilling. Original ID # V-76-I-1.
  - AFC 1970/001: MV025, 1 videoreel (0 min.): 5 in. (diameter), 1⁄2 in. (width)
    Jean Schilling and Lee Schilling, Cosby, Tennessee; Baillie Brothers, Grand Ole Opry Review, Gatlinburg, Tennessee. Original ID # V-76-J-1.
  - AFC 1970/001: MV026, 1 videoreel (31 min.): 5 in. (diameter), 1⁄2 in. (width)
    Rev. Walter Bailes, Gatlinburg, Tennessee, #2. Original ID # V-76-J-2.
  - AFC 1970/001: MV027, 1 videoreel (30 min., 25 sec.): 5 in. (diameter), 1⁄2 in. (width)
    Beekeeper Uncle Lem Owenby, Elkmont, Tennessee, Original ID # V-76-K-1.
  - AFC 1970/001: MV028, 1 videoreel (31 min., 49 sec.): 5 in. (diameter), 1⁄2 in. (width)
    Washington, D.C.; Smithsonian; Corcoran. Original ID # V-76-L-1.
  - AFC 1970/001: MV029, 1 videoreel (31 min., 5 sec.): 5 in. (diameter), 1⁄2 in. (width)
    Photographs, Drawings, and Sounds. Original ID # V-76-M-1.
  - AFC 1970/001: MV030, 1 videoreel (27 min., 39 sec.): 5 in. (diameter), 1⁄2 in. (width)
    Titles, Graphics l. Original ID # V-76-O-1.
  - AFC 1970/001: MV031, 1 videoreel (29 min., 50 sec.): analog, sound, black and white; 5 in. (diameter), 1⁄2 in. (width)
    Auction, "Carl's," Maryville, Tennessee. Original ID # V-77-A-1.
  - AFC 1970/001: MV032, July 3, 1977, 1 videoreel (32 min., 17 sec.): analog, sound, black and white; 5 in. (diameter), 1⁄2 in. (width)
    Brother Roger Powell, #1. Original ID # V-77-B-1.
  - AFC 1970/001: MV033, July 3, 1977, 1 videoreel (32 min., 20 sec.): analog, sound, black and white; 5 in. (diameter), 1⁄2 in. (width)
    Brother Roger Powell, #2. Original ID # V-77-B-2.
  - AFC 1970/001: MV034, July 7, 1977, 1 videoreel (32 min., 31 sec.): analog, sound, black and white; 5 in. (diameter), 1⁄2 in. (width)
    Revival #1, Rev. Ken Ivey, Lafollette, Tennessee. Original ID # V-77-D-1.
  - AFC 1970/001: MV035, July 7, 1977, 1 videoreel (25 min., 23 sec.): analog, sound, black and white; 5 in. (diameter), 1⁄2 in. (width)
    Revival #2, Rev. Ken Ivey, Lafollette, Tennessee. Original ID # V-77-D-2.
  - AFC 1970/001: MV036, July 15, 1977, 1 videoreel (32 min., 20 sec.): analog, sound, black and white; 5 in. (diameter), 1⁄2 in. (width)